<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on KJ&#39;s career development blog site</title>
    <link>/categories/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on KJ&#39;s career development blog site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>R Analysis of Beachbody Workout and Smart Watch Data</title>
      <link>/2022/09/12/r-analysis-of-beachbody-workout-and-smart-watch-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/12/r-analysis-of-beachbody-workout-and-smart-watch-data/</guid>
      <description>What I Learned From My Beachbody Workouts and Fitness Watch DataIntroductionI was looking for an analysis hobby project to dust off my R programming and data analysis skills after over two years since completing my Master’s program. Thinking about the data I accumulate in my everyday life, I started wondering what my Beachbody online workout data would tell me.
I began using Beachbody products in 2013 when my husband bought the DVD version of original P90x program with instructor Tony Horton, which we completed together to prepare for a Mui Thai Kickboxing class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Shiny App Correlation Coefficient</title>
      <link>/2022/09/06/r-shiny-app-correlation-coefficient/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/06/r-shiny-app-correlation-coefficient/</guid>
      <description>BackgroundThis post was created using my 2021 Pennsylvania State University (PSU) Stat 485 class project as a way for me as a student to learn R programming language and associated RStudio IDE. I’ve copied the code as I created it during the class and re-hosted the app in a new location given that I am no longer a student.
This tutorial will review the source code which generates the Shiny App as demonstrated below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
