<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KJ&#39;s career development blog site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KJ&#39;s career development blog site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Wait To Have Your Best Career</title>
      <link>/2022/09/04/dont-wait-to-have-your-best-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/04/dont-wait-to-have-your-best-career/</guid>
      <description>Are you feeling bored at work, stalled in your career progression, or ready for more than just a paycheck from your job? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re just starting your career and wondering if everybody else knows something about being successful that you don&amp;rsquo;t.
Resignation, burnout and boomerang are all hot topics relating to careers in America recently, but I want to share an overlooked subject that I wish I had given more attention to when I started my career as an engineer over 20 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips-n-Tricks</title>
      <link>/tips-n-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 16:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tips-n-tricks/</guid>
      <description> Create catchy blog titles by using seopressor.com/blog-title-generator. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Credits First This site was inspired by the ASA Committee on Career Development Portfolio Project written in Amstat news June 2022. Source code and method follows the fantastic tutorial bookdown by Yihui Xie, Amber Thomas, Alison Presmanes Hill (2022-08-08). Icon sources:
Logo Home from freepnglogos.com 512x512 Logo from freepnglogos.com Linkedin Logo from freepnglogos.com Details This site is built using R language blogdown package and hosted from Netlify connected to my github source code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Development Plan</title>
      <link>/2022/09/02/career-development-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/02/career-development-plan/</guid>
      <description>Preparing For Your Career Road Trip&amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t know where you are going, you might wind up someplace else&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;Yogi Berra
This tutorial will provide an introduction and procedural methodology to creating a development plan.
Why Should You Have A Career Development Plan? What defines a successful career for you?
Does everybody need a plan in order to be successful? No. There&amp;rsquo;s such a thing as luck too. But I bet most people already have a plan in some variant or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
