<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KJ&#39;s career development blog site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KJ&#39;s career development blog site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Most Important Skill To Build My First Web App</title>
      <link>/2022/10/04/the-most-important-skill-to-build-my-first-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/10/04/the-most-important-skill-to-build-my-first-web-app/</guid>
      <description>The Most Important Skill To Build My First Web App It&amp;rsquo;s been 1 week into my new challenge to build a full stack web application. Although I have extensive programming experience with languages such as python and c++, I&amp;rsquo;m fairly new into the realm of web or phone apps which requires front-end and back-end development, plus hosting platforms and data storage services to stitch together. Getting started has been much tougher than I expected!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Analysis of Beachbody Workout and Smart Watch Data</title>
      <link>/2022/09/12/r-analysis-of-beachbody-workout-and-smart-watch-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/12/r-analysis-of-beachbody-workout-and-smart-watch-data/</guid>
      <description>What I Learned From My Beachbody Workouts and Fitness Watch DataIntroductionI was looking for an analysis hobby project to dust off my R programming and data analysis skills after over two years since completing my Master’s program. Thinking about the data I accumulate in my everyday life, I started wondering what my Beachbody online workout data would tell me.
I began using Beachbody products in 2013 when my husband bought the DVD version of original P90x program with instructor Tony Horton, which we completed together to prepare for a Mui Thai Kickboxing class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Shiny App Correlation Coefficient</title>
      <link>/2022/09/06/r-shiny-app-correlation-coefficient/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/06/r-shiny-app-correlation-coefficient/</guid>
      <description>BackgroundThis post was created using my 2021 Pennsylvania State University (PSU) Stat 485 class project as a way for me as a student to learn R programming language and associated RStudio IDE. I’ve copied the code as I created it during the class and re-hosted the app in a new location given that I am no longer a student.
This tutorial will review the source code which generates the Shiny App as demonstrated below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Create A Meaningful Career Development Plan</title>
      <link>/2022/09/05/how-to-create-a-meaningful-career-development-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/05/how-to-create-a-meaningful-career-development-plan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t know where you are going, you might wind up someplace else&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;Yogi Berra
This post continues from the introduction which can be found here: Don&amp;rsquo;t Wait to Have Your Best Career. It introduces a procedural methodology to create a career development plan so that you can obtain your version of a successful career.
The journey is comprised of these steps:
Build Your Compass: Know Thyself Understand The Landscape Map Orientation Locate Your Starting Point Choose Your Destination Plan Your Route Get Moving Reflect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Wait To Have Your Best Career</title>
      <link>/2022/09/04/dont-wait-to-have-your-best-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/04/dont-wait-to-have-your-best-career/</guid>
      <description>Are you feeling bored at work, stalled in your career progression, or ready for more than just a paycheck from your job? Does your profile read &amp;ldquo;successful&amp;rdquo; but you still lack a sense of achievement? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re just starting your career and wondering if everybody else knows something about achieving success that you don&amp;rsquo;t.
Resignation and burnout are recent hot topics relating to careers in America, but I want to share an overlooked subject that I wish I had given more attention to when I started my career as an engineer over 20 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips-n-Tricks</title>
      <link>/tips-n-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 16:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tips-n-tricks/</guid>
      <description>For the Fellow Blogger: Create catchy blog titles by using seopressor.com/blog-title-generator. Although you may not use the titles, they may help you focus on a central theme for a post which may be appealing for a wider audience.
A simple code template to split a longer blog into multiple pages was obatined from this blogtimenow.com post. I then added &amp;lsquo;scrollTo&amp;rsquo; to each navigation so that the window appears at the top of the context instead of at the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Kristi JohnsonData Scientist, Programmer, Engineer, Manager, Mentor, Dog MomBorn/Live: California, USAI have have been an engineer for over 20 years, starting with my first internship in 1997 during college where I learned to love software automation, drawing histograms and applying visualizations, math and statistics to manufacturing and test challenges.
After graduating with a B.S in Computer Engineering, my professional roles required software development and hardware debug to deliver a product, but I continued to be drawn to using data and visualizations to excel at debug and problem solving.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
