<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KJ&#39;s career development blog site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KJ&#39;s career development blog site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>R Shiny App Correlation Coefficient</title>
      <link>/2022/09/06/r-shiny-app-correlation-coefficient/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/06/r-shiny-app-correlation-coefficient/</guid>
      <description>BackgroundThis post was created from a 2021 Pennsylvania State University (PSU) Stat 485 class project as a way for students to learn R and associated RStudio IDE. I’ve copied the code as I created it during the class and re-hosted the app in a new location given that I am no longer a student.
This tutorial will review the source code which generates the Shiny App as demonstrated below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Create A Meaningful Career Development Plan</title>
      <link>/2022/09/05/how-to-create-a-meaningful-career-development-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/05/how-to-create-a-meaningful-career-development-plan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t know where you are going, you might wind up someplace else&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;Yogi Berra
This post continues from the introduction which can be found here: Don&amp;rsquo;t Wait to Have Your Best Career. It introduces a procedural methodology to create a career development plan so that you can obtain your version of a successful career.
The journey is comprised of these steps:
Build Your Compass: Know Thyself Understand The Landscape Map Orientation Locate Your Starting Point Choose Your Destination Plan Your Route Get Moving Reflect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Wait To Have Your Best Career</title>
      <link>/2022/09/04/dont-wait-to-have-your-best-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/04/dont-wait-to-have-your-best-career/</guid>
      <description>Are you feeling bored at work, stalled in your career progression, or ready for more than just a paycheck from your job? Does your profile read &amp;ldquo;successful&amp;rdquo; but you still lack a sense of achievement? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re just starting your career and wondering if everybody else knows something about achieving success that you don&amp;rsquo;t.
Resignation and burnout are recent hot topics relating to careers in America, but I want to share an overlooked subject that I wish I had given more attention to when I started my career as an engineer over 20 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips-n-Tricks</title>
      <link>/tips-n-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 16:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tips-n-tricks/</guid>
      <description>For the Fellow Blogger: Create catchy blog titles by using seopressor.com/blog-title-generator. Although you may not use the titles, they may help you focus on a central theme for a post which may be appealing for a wider audience.
A simple code template to split a longer blog into multiple pages was obatined from this blogtimenow.com post. I then added &amp;lsquo;scrollTo&amp;rsquo; to each navigation so that the window appears at the top of the context instead of at the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Credits First This site was inspired by the ASA Committee on Career Development Portfolio Project written in Amstat news June 2022. Source code and method follows the fantastic tutorial bookdown by Yihui Xie, Amber Thomas, Alison Presmanes Hill (2022-08-08). Icon sources:
Logo Home from freepnglogos.com 512x512 Logo from freepnglogos.com Linkedin Logo from freepnglogos.com Details This site is built using R language blogdown package and hosted from Netlify connected to my github source code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
