<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Career on KJ&#39;s career development blog site</title>
    <link>/categories/career/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Career on KJ&#39;s career development blog site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Create A Meaningful Career Development Plan</title>
      <link>/2022/09/05/how-to-create-a-meaningful-career-development-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/05/how-to-create-a-meaningful-career-development-plan/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t know where you are going, you might wind up someplace else&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;Yogi Berra
This post continues from the introduction which can be found here: Don&amp;rsquo;t Wait to Have Your Best Career. It introduces a procedural methodology to create a career development plan so that you can obtain your version of a successful career.
The journey is comprised of these steps:
Build Your Compass: Know Thyself Understand The Landscape Map Orientation Choose Your Destination Locate Your Starting Point Plan Your Route Get Moving Reflect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Wait To Have Your Best Career</title>
      <link>/2022/09/04/dont-wait-to-have-your-best-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/04/dont-wait-to-have-your-best-career/</guid>
      <description>Are you feeling bored at work, stalled in your career progression, or ready for more than just a paycheck from your job? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re just starting your career and wondering if everybody else knows something about being successful that you don&amp;rsquo;t.
Resignation, burnout and boomerang are all hot topics relating to careers in America recently, but I want to share an overlooked subject that I wish I had given more attention to when I started my career as an engineer over 20 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
